I've been thinking about getting Britney
a juicer for Christmas.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. I've been seeing her drink a lot
of orange juice recently. What do you
think, Shel?
>> I think whatever you get her will be
fine.
>> You know, talking that way doesn't help
me.
>> I'm sorry, Astro.
>> No, no, it's it's fine.
>> I uh didn't know the flash was on, you
know.
>> No, no. Yeah, I I know.
>> I don't know if Brightney drinks enough
juice to warrant getting her a juicer.
Do you want me to ask?
>> That would be feet. I mean, neat. That
would be neat.
>> I um I think I'm going to make like a
bakery truck and move my buns.
>> You don't have to go Astro. We still
didn't pick a movie to watch.
>> I need to do some late evening Christmas
shopping before Sprouts holiday party.
Anyway,
>> I should go, too. Somebody's got to pick
up that juicer for brightening.
>> I'll come too. The juicer might be
heavy.
>> I can come too in case Astro's feet get
tired. I'll give him a foot rub. I think
I'd be especially good at getting my
fingers between those cute little
toesies of his.
>> No thanks.
>> Can you guys not tell the other tunes
about this?
>> Yeah, we won't say anything.
>> I don't think we can do that in good
conscience.
>> That's fair.
I'll delete the picture.
>> You don't have to do that. No, deleting
it might be a good idea.
>> Make sure to go in the trash bin and
delete it there, too, to make sure it's
gone for good.
>> Well, duh, [__] I know how phones
work. Why don't I ever get invited to
Sprout's stupid holiday parties?
>> Because you say he's ugly right to his
face every goddamn day.
>> We got to hit the malls before they
close. We're not going to find any gifts
that could help us win Sprout's special
holiday spanking just standing around. A
holiday spanking from Sprout.
>> You know, Dandy, it's tradition. Every
tune gives Sprout a present. And
whoevers he likes best, he bends them
over his knee and gives them a spanking
in the middle of his living room while
everyone else is made to watch in shame,
wishing it was them being spanked.
>> He does that? I mean, not like I
constantly dream about what it'd be like
for Sprout to spank me or anything. I
think it's rigged because he just picks
Roger every year for some reason. But
that doesn't stop everyone from trying.
>> None of you be jealous now. We all put
thoughts and care into our gifts. I'm
sure Sprout picks the winner fair and
square. It's not weird that I won 24
years in a row. In other words, I never
lost once.
>> Pebble, is that a note for me, boy? Give
it here. And it's red just like all the
invitations Sprout gives out for his
gettogethers. Oh god, this is the best
day of my life. Dear Dandy, you are
cordially uninvited from my Christmas
party. Have fun being all by yourself
again this year, dork. And I bet you're
all still going to go, aren't you? You
nefarious lesbian. We'll bring you back
some cake.
>> Yeah, we can't miss out. You know,
Sprout always orders the good ones from
BaskinRobins.
>> I don't want to hear another word unless
it's Astro saying he wants to put his
feet next to my nostrils. Get out.
I guess it's just going to be you and me
alone again this year, Pebble. But
that's fine. I wouldn't want it any
other way. Pebble,
why are you dressed like you're going
out? What's that tape to your side?
Don't tell me Sprout invited you, but
not me. Take that bow tie off. You're
not going out dressed like that, you
hussy. You get back here.
What are you doing? Put down my car
keys.
>> I hate Christmas. Shrimpo, merry
Christmas.
>> Yeah, I'm talking to you, Shrimpo. Are
you coming to Sprout's party tonight?
>> Goob stop, I told you to not talk to
him. No tune in town like Shrimpo.
>> Shrimpo, you're still in bed.
>> Don't just walk into my house uninvited,
Finn.
>> But it's Christmas. You're supposed to
be around your friends on Christmas.
>> Having friends is gay.
>> Come on, it ain't so bad. You just got
to wrap your head around the spirit of
things. Get it? Wrap like presents. Do
you want to go to the mall? That always
cheers you up, big man.
>> I'd rather you shut up and make me
tomato soup and a grilled cheese
sandwich and put on that maid dress I
bought you like a good [__]
The tomato soup is still cold.
>> I'll go put it back in the microwave for
you, Daddy.
>> Don't bother, sexy boy. I'm going back
to bed. My hands are freezing. The
winter is a cold time for a badass
shrimp.
>> Do you want me to warm them up for you?
>> Miss me with that gay [__] you
temptress. Punk ass [__] I will fart
in your mouth if you try that again. God
damn it, my hands are cold.
Well, if it isn't Finn the sexy fishbowl
doing some late night Christmas shopping
before Sprouts party. Not for Sprout,
for Shrimpo. He was saying his hands
were cold, so I wanted to get him some
gloves. Well, those ones you were
looking at are just sublime. I'm sure he
will like anything you pick because your
best friends, Astro, what up, buttercup?
Do you ever have you ever, you know, cut
yourself? Sometimes when Shrimpo
Shrimpo hit me this morning, I know he
does stuff like that because he's
hurting inside, so I just let him do it
without getting mad. But because I don't
have anyone else to take my own
frustration out on, I turn on myself.
And I Never mind. What I'm saying is
stupid. Okay.
Do you think if I gave Danny this
powdered lemonade for Christmas, he'd
let me ask for some pictures of his feet
in return? Or would that be a weird
trade? Hey, Astro, you and Sprout's
butts are about the same size, right?
Stop talking to the toilet bowl. I need
you to go into the dressing room and try
them on so I can know if they'd fit,
Sprout.
Omg, Flutter, you naughty little
butterfly creature. You got me a juicer.
Just what I always wanted.
>> Well, [__] got a juicer.
>> Hey, Sprout. I got you this juicer.
>> A what? A juicer?
How dare you do this to him? Get out.
Get out of our loving strawberry home,
you wicked woman. Cosmo, shut up. What
are you trying to say, [__] Do you
know how many strawberry friends I lost
to things like that?
>> Oh, I uh cheese and crackers. You're a
strawberry. God damn it, Shelly. I
messed up.
>> Here's your present, Sprout. Do you
maybe you know want to open it right
now?
>> Ear muffs.
>> Aren't you, you know, going to give me
something in return now, [__] Like a
spanking on my behind mayhaps?
>> Is this some kind of joke to make fun of
me for not having ears?
>> Oh, balls. No, I I' I'd never do that. I
don't have ears either. Actually, I
don't think any of us have got ears.
>> Do you know how hard I've got it
already? Not being able to hear [__]
how I've got to read mouths just to get
by in life.
>> Well, yeah. None of us have got ears, so
we all do that.
>> Cosmo, take this and throw it in the
fireplace with the rest of the trash.
Sprout, look. Pebble got your invite.
Hey there, Pebble. Are you excited to be
here? Now, hold on a second, boy. You're
not seriously thinking you're going to
be allowed inside, are you? You were
never really invited to my party. I just
called you here because I needed a [__]
close to Dandy to send a message back
for me.
Look, Finn, Shrimpo's already at the
party. Go give him your present. Do you
really think he'll like it? Of course he
will, because it's from you. Just
believe in yourself. Hey, uh, Shrimpo,
merry Christmas. You know I hate
Christmas. I am only here for some free
Dr. Pepper and then I'm going home.
Before you do that, I got something for
you.
>> Are you being dead ass? Don't you want
to give this to Barry Boy and try and
win his Christmas spanking?
>> I was thinking of the ultimate Rizzler
when I saw this at the mall. My best
friend, just open it.
>> You think I've got Riz? Well, okay.
It's a pair of gloves. You said your
hands were cold this morning. I picked
the orange ones because you know you're
a shrimp and shrimps are orange. So,
you're just giving me your trash?
>> What? No, I just thought that.
>> No, you didn't. You never think that's
why nobody in Garden View likes you. My
hands were cold. Only because you forgot
to heat up MY TOMATO SOUP. I TELL YOU
all the time, the only gift I ever want
is $100.
Go refill my cup with Dr. Pepper before
I hit you again.
You deserve to be hit if you really gave
him cold tomato soup this morning. Don't
talk to me, Astro. You ruined my
Christmas. Just walk away with your
powdered lemonade. Stupid idea of a
gift. I'm not going to stand here and be
made fun of by an abused fishbowl
housewife who cuts himself. How dare
you? I shared that information in a
vulnerable moment. Well, then that is
your mistake for thinking I wouldn't use
it as ammo to verbally assault you.
Tounes are not caring beings by nature,
Finn.
>> Hey, Goob. I got you a little something.
Merry Christmas.
>> Look, Goob. Somebody who cares about you
even though you're autistic.
>> A gift from Shrimpo. Oh, this is the
best day of my life.
>> I was thinking of you when I saw this
cause you've got RZ. So, just open it.
Wow. Shoes.
>> No, you goober. They're gloves. I wasn't
sure what color you'd like. So, I picked
orange ones because I'm a shrimp and
shrimps are orange and I know you like
shrimps. At least I hope you do. Of
course, I love shrimps because you are
one and you're my best friend. I love
you, Shrimpo.
Stop. This is mine.
>> Shelly, what is that?
>> It's the blingy cup I got from the mall.
I'm going to give it to Sprout when
nobody else is around so I can win the
birthday spanking. Hey,
>> I'm giving this to Brightney. Leave me
alone.
>> Why are you so dead set on giving
Britney a Christmas present? I barely
even see you talk to her.
>> Because I want Brighton to sit on my
face. Okay.
>> The the lampshade.
So, Sprout dear, what is it that you
have planned as entertainment for this
evening?
>> Oh, you want special entertainment, huh?
Well, I'll give you entertainment.
>> Start playing Jingle Bell Rock. Um,
actually, that's okay, Sprout. We can
entertain ourselves just fine. You don't
get a say in how I treat my property.
I don't even have an instrument. What do
I play?
>> Your job is to do the only thing you're
good at up there.
Leave it to Sprout to get Rudy to show
off his goods for free. They should be
worshiping me. Nobody else.
Well, well, well. Look who was kicked
out of Sprout's party.
You never got inside.
You tried asking him to let you in and
he kicked you in the face.
>> He invited you just so he could
humiliate you. Oh my poor Rock, who is
also a dog. Come here.
Okay, here's what's going down, boy.
You're going to hold on to this rope
while I climb down the chimney because
all the tunes of Gardens View are down
there partying their scrumptious butts
off, humiliating themselves all in some
deranged hope that Sprout spanks them
before the end of the night. I'm
supposed to be the star of the show. Me,
Dandy's world. If I surprise everybody
down there and give each of them a $25
Robux gift card that will remind them
whose world they're really living in.
You're doing good, Pebble. Good boy.
Just a little bit lower. I know I'm
heavy boy, but I can't help it when my
butt cheeks are the size of an actual
dump truck.
>> I heard Sprout didn't invite Dandy again
this year.
>> Well, can you blame Sprout? Dandy always
tries to make every situation about him.
>> Hold on, Pebble. These [__] are
gossiping about me. I want to hear the
dirt they spew when their rainbow pedal
god isn't hovering over them like a pair
of butt cheeks over a toilet. Balloon
[__] boy is right. Like, I wouldn't be
surprised if Dandy was dressed up as a
gay little elf and climbing down the
chimney in this very moment so he could
steal all the attention away from Sprout
and make Christmas all about him. The
places your mind goes is hilarious
sometimes. Yada, is it cuz you're
Mexican?
>> Well, that and because I have autism and
because I really don't like fat people,
even though I'm kind of fat myself.
>> Pebble, just just pull me back up. I'm
going home.
It doesn't matter what that chica said
about me. Just pull me back up.
>> What's that sound?
>> I farted, but I did it quietly, hoping
you wouldn't have heard it.
>> No, I MEAN IT SOUNDS like it's coming
from the chimney.
>> Well, I still farted and also pooped a
little bit, so don't walk behind me.
>> You crazy [__] Wait here. I'll go
check it out. Pebble, quick, pull me up.
Pebble.
Well, well, well. Look who has blessed
this berry boy's bodacious butt cheeks
with his flowery presence. What do you
want, Sprout? I should be asking you
that queer. You're the one in my
chimney.
>> I'm not a queer. I am heterosexual. The
animalistic desires I have for other
boys means nothing if I do not act upon
them.
>> Oh god, thank you for sending this dweeb
to me under this position. The other
tunes aren't going to believe it when I
call them all here and show them how
much of a loser you're being. Just help
me climb back up and I'll go home. I
will not perform a humiliation ritual
for a strawberry. Oh yeah, you are.
You're going to be dancing around like
the little monkey you are for all our
friends. Hey everybody, come look at
this. Hey. Hey, stop. Get back here.
>> What is it, Sprout? It's Dandy. He was
the one in my chimney.
>> I don't see him.
>> He was just here. It was weird. He was
dressed in a tiny green Christmas
costume and everything for some reason.
>> You mean like a silly little elf? Like a
baby, but sexy. You know, like like a
sexy [__]
>> Sprout. Maybe you've been out in the
cold for a minute too long.
>> I'm being dead ass. I'm not going crazy.
Quick, come over here and you'll see his
footprints in the snow.
Tisha. Tisha, what are you doing?
>> I'm sweeping because it's the only thing
I'm good at.
>> Did you sweep up any footprints while
you were down there?
>> Well, I've never not been down here.
>> Did you or did you not sweep up
footprints, though?
>> I don't know. I don't really pay
attention to what I'm sweeping. I just
kind of do it.
>> Well, you destroyed the only evidence
that proves Dandy was at my house.
>> How do you know he was here? There's not
any footprints.
>> That's what I'm saying. I came over to
show them his footprints. There's not
any down here.
>> Yeah, cuz you swept them up.
>> I just told you I don't know if they
were here before I started sweeping.
>> Sprout Tisha is not neurotypical. She
doesn't get what you're saying. Annie
was never here. I was with him at his
house this morning where he was taking
pictures of my feet.
>> That's why he was being sneaky about it.
You dweebs aren't listening. Sprout, I
love you, but your obsession with Dandy
lately is starting to make me
uncomfortable.
WAIT, WHY am I the one running away? I
have a gun.
>> You really tried coming in through the
back entrance, [__] You thought. How
stupid can one flower be? Sprout, look
in Dandy's smelly butt crack. Powdered
lemonade. You've been wanting this all
week, but they've been all out at the
store. Dandy, did you bring that here
for me? Well, it's Christmas and you
know I don't show up to any tunes house
without a gift because I'm godamn
Danakus Dandifer after all. Garden View
is my town. So I got to make sure that
y'all [__] know who's the top
provider here.
You made a big ass mistake getting me
that gift. You know I did. How so? Every
tune in Garden View knows that the silly
little tune who gets me my favorite gift
of the evening gets a silly little slap
on their silly little cheeks until
they're red and glistening. Oh yeah?
Well, every two knows that. But surely
my stupid little thingy of powdered
lemonade couldn't possibly have been
yours. Okay, Sprout, it's almost
midnight. It's time to tell everybody to
go home.
Oh, wow. Someone knows how to use their
tongue.
Ah,
>> I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
>> You kissed what belongs to me. Everybody
saw.
>> I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. A dirty
tune like me was born.
>> It's so tough belonging to the most
popular tune in Garden View. Everyone
wants me, it seems.
Ew. What's up with Astro's arms?
>> YEAH. WHY'S he got four of them? Someone
set him on fire.
>> Who's got ammo now, [__]
You seeing this [__] Finn? Oh, I'm
seeing it, Shrimpo. I've got my eyes all
over him. Circus trio, take him away.
Ah, Tisha, can we use that giant wooden
tea I gave you for your birthday to set
him on fire with?
>> You have my permission.
Sprout, you're going too far. It's not
Astro's fault. He was born an ugly freak
of nature. This is a new low even for
you, Sprout. No, it's not. I make fun of
other tunes for having physical
differences all the time.
Stop it, Sprout. You're treating him
like Jesus Christ. That's right. If you
kill him, he will become a martyr just
like Jesus became.
>> Yeah. Killing him will only inspire
other tunes to be different like him.
>> Okay, I don't care as long as those
other tunes don't have four arms because
forearms is weird.
>> Oh my god. He was hiding one of his
freaky forearms behind his back and with
a knife.
>> A dang it. He's getting away.
>> Peace out, [__]
>> Hey, stop.
>> Oh, bother not dial.
>> Dandicus.
>> Dial.
>> Happy holidays to you.
>> I need to go in there. Astro is having
one of his tantrums again.
>> I see that.
You've got something on your face.
>> Keep your filthy paws off me, Dial. It's
soot from Sprouts chimney, that's all. I
don't even know why I'm wasting my
breath on you. You know I don't talk to
tunes who swing that way.
>> Are you implying you don't?
>> No, I don't. Not anymore. You made sure
of that.
You taught me that there's no such thing
as true love between two boys. If there
were such a thing, you and I would still
be in the same place we were a year ago.
delightful.
>> I need to go find Astro
>> running away from me again then.
>> How could you possibly blame me for
anything when you're the one who tossed
me aside? All because you want the main
character role to yourself. You simply
can't stand the thought of your peers
glancing over to look at the tune your
arm is linked with and seeing them as
your equal. You want everyone's eyes on
only yourself.
>> And is that so wrong? Having self-ride
about being a bad [__]
>> You can be the baddest [__] in Garden
View, but if you ain't got no [__]
yourself are the sacrifices you made
that led you to being the top [__]
really worth it.
I still love you for what it's worth,
even if it's unrequited. Dandicus,
>> you must be cold without your anxiety
blanket.
>> I shouldn't have kissed Cosmo. I did it
to make Sprout mad. Well, if you asked
me that strawberry [__] Twink deserved
it for being a bully to you. If you had
told me he was being that way to you at
the party, I would have taken you and we
would have gotten out of there together.
You know, I didn't even want to be
there.
>> Sprout actually wasn't bullying me up
until I did that. I was the one who
started it.
>> Why did you want to make him mad?
>> It's childish, but I was jealous when he
said he was going to, you know, spank
you. Listen, Astro, I don't get why
every tune in Garden View is so dead set
on wanting to be spanked by Sprout. But
if you wanted to be spanked by him that
bad, maybe you should have gotten him a
better gift than the lemonade I brought.
Haha.
>> Oh, Dandy, you really don't get it at
all.
We're sitting this close already. Do you
maybe want to
>> Astro? Absolutely not. You know what
this day is? Christmas isn't about that.
It's about Jesus, his birthday.
>> It would only be a silly little kiss.
>> Even that is too much. Boys kissing boys
is the gravest of sins, Astro. The
gravest. Would Jesus have put his tongue
into Judas's mouth if he asked? No
chance. Temptation is how it starts.
Even if we give in for a second, we'll
be scarred. And those scars which may
appear invisible now will be completely
visible when we stand before God. Then
all that's left for us is hell. But it
is like a Christmas rule that a boy
should kiss another boy if they find
themselves under the mistletoe. Perhaps
even God can have a sense of humor from
time to time.
Are you as scarred as you were afraid
you'd become?
Dandy, I'm sorry. Oh, baby girl, wait.
>> I did something sinful today, Pebble.
Wish you a merry Christmas. We wish you
a merry Christmas and a happy new year.
Tidings we
wish you a merry Christmas and a happy
new year.
>> We won't go until we get some.
Dandy, what's good? Rudy the caked up
reindeer and everyone else is whose
names I'm struggling to remember. What
are you all doing here?
>> I'm here to show you my new shoes. I
realized how much of a butt I was being
by not inviting you to my party since
I'm cool as crap. Of course you try to
sneak in and be part of the the fun. So
I thought, what better way to put this
whole thing behind us than to bring the
party to you, big dog. Well, y'all
turned this from sad to cringey real
fast. You know, it's like 1:00 in the
morning, right? Oh, it is? Yeah. It
ain't even Christmas anymore. I don't
want to party. So, get off my lawn
before I go get my gun.
Oh, hey there sexy viewers. Sprout here.
Did you like today's episode of Dandy's
World? If so, why not subscribe to
Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 over on Patreon for as
little as $3. Your sexy name will appear
at the end of episodes like the one
scrolling by now next to my fat ass that
lets losers know you support the good
[__] and helps tamers produce Dandy's
World cartoons even faster. Also, if you
join now, you get a limited time special
Christmas wallpaper with yours truly and
dial to celebrate the holidays. There's
also gifts and [__] I'm on the
wallpaper, too. Shut up, Dandy. This
isn't about you. Hurry and get it while
you can before Christmas is over.
Christmas is already over. What? It's
not Christmas anymore. Oh, well, go get
it anyway, [__]
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
Heat
up here.
Yeah.
Heat.